### Contact

+91 8688088368 (Work) venkatasudheermanda@gmail.c om

www.linkedin.com/in/venkatasudheer (LinkedIn) venkatasudheerportfolio.herokuapp.c (Portfolio)

## Top Skills

jQuery

PHP

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

## Languages

Telugu (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

### Certifications

PHP

**HTML** 

Google digital unlocked Facebook Spilt Testing Google analytics

#### **Publications**

Fingerprint Based Online Payment System

# Manda Venkatasudheerkumar

Software Developer at Thinkinfinity Technology and Consulting Chennai

## Summary

Experienced Certification Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, C++, Java, Networking, and HTML. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor of Technology (B Tech) focused in CSE from SRM University.

# Experience

Thinkinfinity Technology and Consulting Software Developer January 2021 - Present (3 months) Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

## Google Developers

google assistant developer community program member September 2019 - Present (1 year 7 months)

I Have Made Action On Google. Action On Google is The Development Platform For Google Assistant. Google Assistant is an Artificial Intelligence-powered Virtual Assistant Developed By Google that was Primarily Available on Mobile Devices and Smart Home. Unlike the Company's Previous Virtual Assistant, Google Now, Google Assistant can engage in a two-way conversation. In 2017, the Google Assistant was installed on more than 400 million devices.

Name of My Action is "Ravi Traders". This actions is for chilli powder business.

To Use:

Trigger Google Assistant By:

"OK Google, Talk To Ravi Traders"

OR

you can check my action in https://www.ravimanda.co.in/contact.php page

India Studio
Web Developer
October 2020 - January 2021 (4 months)
Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

90bar2

Web Developer

January 2020 - September 2020 (9 months)

Chennai Area, India

- 1. created Static website
- 2. created Ecommerce Mobile Application using Framework7

live demo: https://90bar2.com/ecomerce/

webprogr.com
Software Engineer

January 2019 - January 2020 (1 year 1 month)

Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

After entering in to this company i have learned how to make hybrid apps with the help of cordova (to genrate APK).

What i have learned after joining in this company

- 1 Mobile Ui
- 2 Framework7
- 3 Quasar Framework
- 4 Vue js

My projects:

Hybrid app:https://www.amazon.com/Ravi-Traders/dp/B07MZPCXCN/

website:https://www.ravimanda.co.in , https:livenews.ravimanda.co.in using vue js

portfolio example: https://venkatasudheerportfolio.herokuapp.com using vue.js

portfolio: https://venkatasudheer.8b.io

IIHT Ltd

**Certification Courses** 

March 2018 - July 2018 (5 months)

Chennai Area, India

I have done with A+(Hardware) and N+(Networking)

In that Courses i have learnt

Hardware:

- 1) Hardware Components of the Computer and Basic things like the types of Processors and ROMS and RAMS
- 2) Architecture of the Computer
- 3) Assemble and Reassemble of the Computer hardware parts
- 4) How to Install Software's in the Computer from Bootloader
- 5) How to break the Computer Password with the help of some software's
- 6) How to dual windows in single Computer Networking :
- 1) how to route the IP Address from one router to another router
- 2) how to send Messages from Router -Switch Router
- 3) How to Configure the Router and Switch
- 4) Network Layers

HP sotware university Internship July 2017 - August 2017 (2 months) Chennai Area, India

I m learning about Hadoop and Big data(HIV, PIG)

JP Infotech Inplant Training July 2016 - July 2016 (1 month) Chennai Area, India

I have done PHP, HTML and CSS. And learnt how to code using them in Eclipse.

# Education

SRM University

Bachelor of Technology (BTech), Computer Science Engineering · (2014 - 2018)

Sri Chaitanya College of Education

INTERMEDIATE , Maths, Physics, Chemistry · (2012 - 2014)

Triveni Public School 10th Class, State Board · (2011 - 2012)